dreamscashtrue.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | Dreams Cash True

Our Privacy Policy discloses what information we collect and how it is used

We always respect your privacy and do our best to protect your personal information. Our Privacy Policy below discloses what information we collect, how it is used and what we do to safeguard it. We will never sell your personal information to third-parties.

## Mailing Lists

We only collect the names and email addresses of subscribers who have voluntarily opted-in to receive our periodic newsletters. We hold this information confidentially and do not release or disclose it under any circumstances, unless demanded by law.

## Log Files

As most websites, we collect and make use of data contained in log files. The collected information includes your internet protocol (IP) address, the type of browser used, your internet service provider (ISP), the date and time you visited our website and which pages you visited throughout our website. We use this data to analyze usage trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around our website, and gather demographic information. Your IP address and other information collected in log files are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store personal preference information when you visit our website. Cookies can be used to personalize your browsing experience. This could include only showing you a popup once during your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as premium content areas.

We use third-party advertisements to support our website. Some of our advertisers may use technologies such as cookies, DART cookies or web beacons when they advertise on our website. These technologies send the advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, the type of browser used, your ISP, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. Such cookies are generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing San Diego real estate ads to someone in San Diego, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific websites visited (such as showing investing ads to someone who frequents investing websites). The use of DART cookies enables advertisers such as Google AdSense to serve ads based on your visit to our website and other websites on the Internet.  You may opt out of the use of DART cookies by visiting [Google Advertising Policies and Principles](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences through programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our website, as well as other websites, including the inability to login to services or programs, such as premium content areas or user accounts.

## Information Collected by Third-Parties

We may allow third-party companies that use tracking technologies, such as cookies or pixels, to record IP address information about users who visit or interact with our website. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third-parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers [a single location](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.

## Security of Information

We use reasonable measures to maintain the security of the information we collect. However, no company, organization, or online community, including **Dreams Cash True** and its owner **Fortnoff Financial, LLC** , can fully eliminate security risks associated with the collection of information.

## Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, by posting such change, update or modification. Any such change, update or modification shall be effective immediately upon posting.
